http://www.laurashouse.org/privacy-policy

Close Menu
About Us
About UsOur ServicesBoard of DirectorsHistoryPress & MediaTestimonials & Art GalleryOur PartnersWhy Donate?Celebrating 25 Years of ServiceJob Opportunities
Programs & Services
Programs & Services OverviewChildren's ProgramsCounseling & Resource CenterDomestic Violence Advocacy CenterLegal ServicesShelterTransitional HousingH.E.A.R.T. Prevention & EducationOutreach & Education
Get Help
Get HelpSigns of AbuseSafety PlanningHow to Help a FriendStatistics
Resale Stores
Get Involved
Ways to Get Involved - OverviewVolunteer Opportunities40-Hour State Certified TrainingJunior Friends ProgramLaura's House Wish ListDonateSpecial EventsDonate A VehicleFundraise with UsLaura's Legacy SocietyLaura's House GuildShop For A CauseStudent Projects
Contact Us
Teen Site
Español
Donate Today
Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Laura's House respects the privacy and is committed to maintaining the confidentiality of our donors, staff, clients, volunteers, and friends. As a result, we will not sell, rent or share this information or other supporter information with others under any circumstances. Laura's House periodically communicates with donors and friends through emails and other mailings. If you wish to be excluded from these communications, please let us know. For more information, contact Laura's House at 949-361-3775.
Online Donations and/or Event Registrations
Laura's House collects the following information through our secure online credit-card giving page: name, address, e-mail address, phone number, and credit card information. This personally identifiable information is used only to collect your contribution and/or event registration and to acknowledge receipt of your donation for tax purposes.
Online Data Security
Laura's House helps protect personally identifiable information by utilizing both online and offline security methods, including firewalls, passwords and restricted physical access to the places where your information is stored. Our staff is trained to comply with our security procedures, and our security procedures are regularly reviewed and revised, if necessary, by the management of Laura's House.
Our on-line credit giving pages use industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) encryption on all web pages where personal information is required. To make donations through our on-line giving pages, you must use an SSL-enabled browser such as Netscape Navigator 3.0 or later, or Internet Explorer. This protects the confidentiality of your personal and credit card information while it is transmitted over the Internet.
Acceptance of Terms/Changes to Privacy Policy
Your use of this site indicates an acceptance of the terms of the Internet Privacy Policy. Laura's House reserves the right to update or amend this Internet Privacy Policy at any time.
Third Party Service Providers
From time to time, Laura's House may decide that it is more efficient to use third parties to perform specific services. If we use a third party to provide specific services, then information (such as contact information) may be shared with that party to the extent necessary for the third party to provide these services. These third party service providers are only allowed to use personally identifiable information for the purpose of providing the specific services requested by Laura's House. The third party services covered by this paragraph do not include links to third party sites found on our sites, which are governed by a more specific provision below.
Links to Other Web Sites
This site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Laura's House does not exercise control over (and is not responsible for) the information, products, services or policies of third party companies accessible through our site. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy policies of each and every third party site. This Internet Privacy Policy applies solely to the information collected by this site. Your privacy is important to Laura's House. If you have questions about any of the provisions described above, please call us at 949.361.3775.
Refund Policy
Like any tax-deductible charitable contribution, any on-line contribution made to Laura's House cannot be cancelled or returned once it has been completed.
Close
Laura's House
Welcome to Laura's House
Sign up for our newsletter and receive news and updates to everything Laura's House.
Email Address
Close
